<resume xmlns="urn:resume"
        xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/XMLSchema-instance"
        xsi:schemaLocation="urn:resume resume.xsd">
    <contact>
        <name>Bryan Matsuo</name>
        <phone type="mobile">+1 801 671 2514</phone>
        <email>bryan.matsuo@gmail.com</email>
        <website label="GitHub">https://github.com/bmatuso</website>
        <website label="LinkedIn">https://linkedin.com/in/bryanmatsuo</website>
        <website label="Personal">http://bmats.co</website>
    </contact>
    <objective>
        I want to solve hard problems, build and scale backend systems,
        and learn new skills with a talented group of motivated people.
    </objective>
    <skills>
        <skill>Shell Scripting</skill>
        <skill>Ruby on Rails</skill>
        <skill>Perl</skill>
        <skill>Python</skill>
        <skill>Matlab/Matplotlib</skill>
        <skill>Go</skill>
        <skill>Scala</skill>
        <skill>Puppet</skill>
        <skill>MongoDB</skill>
        <skill>Redis</skill>
        <skill>Zookeeper</skill>
        <skill>SQL (Postgres)</skill>
        <skill>Functional Programming</skill>
        <skill>OAuth 2.0</skill>
        <skill>C/C++</skill>
        <skill>Lisp/Scheme</skill>
        <skill>Ocaml</skill>
        <skill>Haskell</skill>
        <skill>Scala</skill>
        <skill>Git</skill>
    </skills>
    <intrests>
        <interest type="work">Web architecture</interest>
        <interest type="work">Distributed systems</interest>
        <interest type="work">Dev Ops</interest>
        <interest type="work">Client-side MV*</interest>
        <interest type="personal">
            Learning programming languages, exploring different problem solving
            mindsets and paradigms, and finding the best tools for different
            problems.
        </interest>
        <interest type="personal">
            Developing tools and automation workflows for home-entertainment
            system PCs, improving their integration with satellite devices
            (laptops, iDevices, etc.).
        </interest>
        <interest type="personal">Soccer</interest>
        <interest type="personal">Music</interest>
        <interest type="personal">Backpacking</interest>
    </intrests>
    <history>
        <employment>
            <organization>Janrain</organization>
            <dates from="Feb 2012" to="present"/>
            <position>Software Engineer</position>
            <description>
                After initially writing integration libraries for OAuth social
                identity providers, I took over development on the primary
                backend component in large-scale redesign for the core user
                management product written in Ruby on Rails. I participated in
                design discussions with product management, developed the
                initial test framework still used for product QA, and was
                responsible for most of the server-side coding involving
                integrating internal services and building a processor for a
                user management DSL. As more, larger customers were brought
                on to the product I worked with operations and software
                egineers from other teams to tune performance of our
                infrastructure to meet the necessary. As that project shifted
                from development to maintenence I've transitioned to a team
                writing Scala web services to tackle infrastructure management
                problems the faced by the company as it grows.
            </description>
        </employment>
        <employment>
            <organization>LEEPS, Univ of California - Santa Cruz</organization>
            <dates from="Apr 2011" to="Jul 2011"/>
            <position>Software Development (Contract)</position>
            <description>
                I developed an open source, network-multiplayer game framework
                for academic use in experimental economics in conjunction with
                lead developer James Pettit. The real-time framework was
                implemented in Python used Redis on the backend for consistent
                state management and a JSON protocal for client communication.
                There was also some GUI programming with GTK, Wx, and Matplotlib.
            </description>
        </employment>
        <education>
            <organization>Univ of Califonia - Santa Cruz</organization>
            <dates fram="Sep 2004" to="Mar 2009"/>
            <degree type="BS" field="Computer Science"/>
            <degree type="BA" field="Mathematics"/>
            <items>
                <item>Honors in Computer Science</item>
                <item>Highest honors in Mathematics</item>
            </items>
        </education>
    </history>
</resume>
